

Edyta Szarowska

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I have been intensively learning web application programming for three years.

I have eight months of commercial experience in creating and maintaining software. I want to develop my competences in finding new solutions during the current problem solving.

TECH STACK

- -HTML -
- -CSS3/SCSS -
- -JavaScript -
- -ReactJS -
- -Next.js -
- -Git/Github/Gitlab -
- -Bootstrap/Chakra UI/StyleComponent -
- -Redux -
- -Sass -

CONTACT DETAILS

Telephone: +48 666 886 255

Email: edyta.szarowska.dev@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://edyta-szarowska-

portfolio.netlify.com/

Github: http://github.com/Edyta2801 LinkedIn: http://linkedin.com/in/edyta-

szarowska/

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT MENTEE

Mentoring Dare IT| 11.2021 - current

Mentoring program during which I work with a mentor on the technical skills of Frontend developer and soft skills (time management, giving feedback, teamwork, Agile, Scrum).

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Innokrea sp. z o.o. | 06.2021 - 08.2021

Work on developing auction applicationj, tech-stack: Next.js, TypeScript,, Redux, Storybook, StyleComponents.

STUDENT IN SZKOŁA REACTA

Szkoła Reacta Patryk Omiotek| 10.2020 -03.2021

Practical use of React, js, Redux oraz Next. js, testing.

WEB DEVELOPER

Agencja Reklamowa Cumulus | 06.2020 - 10.2020

Working mainly with CMS Wordpress, working in the Scrum methodology. I was a project manager for one of the projects.

TRAINEE GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Centrum Szkoleń i Innowacji Sp. z o.o.| 02.2020 - 05.2020

Computer graphics training (ECCC certificate) and internship - practical use of Photoshop and Corel.

BOOTCAMP STUDENTJUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

InfoShare Academy sp. z o.o. |10.2018 - 12.2018

320 hours of training provided knowledge and practical skills in the field of: JavaScript, REST, JSON, AJAX, React, Redux, HTML5 / CSS, Git. Group project in the Scrum methodology.

PYTHON TRAINING STUDENT

InfoShare Academy sp. z o.o. | 01.2018 - 03.2018

45 hours of training in basic programming knowledge in the field of analytical problem solving and creating Python programs.

SPECIALIST IN MSP/BROKER SALES

PZU SA, Lublin | 11.2007 - 08.2018

OUALITY AUDITOR

RHM Avana Bakeries Newport, Wales | 02.2007 - 07.2007

EDUCATION

KOSZALIN UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Master of Management and Marketing Postgraduate Studies Quality Auditor

LANGUAGES

POLISH- NATIVE LANGUAGE ENGLISH- B2

INTEREST

Personal effectiveness, learning to play the piano